[{"answer": "How long", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Four years", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "So, you want a te", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You have it with you", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "On his prior, he served nine months, and he's working on four years' probation", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Do you know what he's on probation for", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "my friend. ", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "House", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "What the fuck can I say? I'm serious, man. What the fuck can I say? Thank you... thank you... thank you", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You were there for me", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "The moon", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You're outside", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Who was that", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Who was that place", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Hear what", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "If there's no", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Why would a stewardess bring me fifty grand", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I understand", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Yes, my friend, I understand", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'll call her", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I won't forget", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "It's kind of a sports ba", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Why does it need to be dark", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "The federal agent kinda half hinted my friend might of done that place", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I didn't", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, my friend, you got caught, you're gonna have to give 'em something", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Give 'em what you got. Offer to help. Show a willingness to be helpful. You want to stay out of jail, don't you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And they asked if I knew Mr. my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "She wants to make a deal", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "She almost sounds scared", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "You never asked me if I did or not", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "'Course I do", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No shit. You know how he makes hi money", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "You ever see him sell guns", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "Short of wearing a wire, I'll do everything I can to help you throw his ass in jail. And in exchange for my help, I need permission to leave the country and immunity", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Can you do it or not", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "I thought you were sixteen", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Were you a disco girl", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "I was pretty much the same height now as I was then", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Noooo, I was a surfer girl. Besides, I was only fourteen. I couldn't go to discos", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Were you a disco girl", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "So where did you go", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I don't like dancing", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "I went to a few just to meet women. But I don't like to dance, and it's so fucki", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You been to that place", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I ain't your partner, I'm your manager. I'm managing to get your money out of that place, into that place, in your hands, and I'm managing to do all this under the nose of the cops. That makes me your manager, and managers get fifteen percent", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "That's an agent. Manager's get fifteen percent", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "\"American Prseiden", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "Pretty good. Me and my friend are goin steady", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "I'm helping him bring his money into that place. He loves the idea. You just missed him", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Yeah, we were goin' over everything. That's why all the bags", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "The day you got me out of jail", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "Wait a minute. After we were together you went and snuck into a guy's house", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": " 'Cause she my fine little surfer gal. She can't do me no harm. Fact she think she can play you against me shows how little she knows. You could teach that bitch for days how it is 'tween me an you, she never understand a damn word", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "I don't hafta trust her, I know her", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "I don't want no more fuckin' surprises. We do this the way I laid it out, or we don't do it at all", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "Sheronda passin' the money onto someone else, that's what the hell I'm talkin' 'bout", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": "She won't have no problems 'cause she don't know nothin'", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "She don't know shit about the money", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "Listen, Miss, I'm waiting for a drink and you spend half the fuckin' flight in the can. Soon as we land I'm making a formal complaint", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "You didn't call me that", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "After all, it don't belong to nobody, right", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Yeah, well, it's not a point of view that A.T.F. shares. Once we make it evidence, it belongs to us. You are now officially out of trouble. Don't do nothing stupid, now", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "It's my friend", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "I got it. Listen, there's something else I have to tell you", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Where's the rest of it", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "Maybe forty, maybe not that much", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "I didn't see him. I was in my underwear. If it was a white guy, it was probably my friend. He kill my friend", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I have no idea", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "We pick up my friend. We've got three murders we can link him to. We have the storage unit where he keeps his guns, by tomorrow we'll have a search warrant to go in and get him. And we have you", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "What about you", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "He's around", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "I'll give you his beeper", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Cops can't locate him, huh", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Sure thing. I don't have to know what I'm doing, long as you know", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "What the fuck you doin' knockin on the door like the goddamn police? You lookin' to get shot", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "You keep fuckin' with me, you're gonna be asleep forever", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "She wants to give you your money. If she didn't, there'd be cops batte", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "Winston found you", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "How'd you find me", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "How the fuck did he find me", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "Winston found you", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "That's what my friend does. He finds people who don't want to be found", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "She wants to give it to you herself and collect her ten percent. She also wants to explain why she had to hold on to it", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "I know where it is", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "I know where to turn", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "We're partners", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "Do you blame yourself for helping me", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": " Where're you going", "docId": "jackiebrown.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "that place or that place", "qsentId": 94}]